warcraftpets.com 2019-04-20

# Privacy Policy - WarcraftPets.com

Any and all information you provide to WarcraftPets is fully protected under this policy. You can browse through most of the site without the need to divulge any personal information. However, an email address is required to complete certain online requests, such as creating an account.

## Email

**You will NEVER receive junk email from WarcraftPets**.

We hate spam as much as you do. We'll keep your email address as safe and confidential as possible. Email addresses submitted to WarcraftPets.com are never shared nor sold to third parties.

Note that an email transmitted to WarcraftPets may not be secure, unless specifically noted prior to transmitting your message. For this reason, it is recommended that you do not send confidential or sensitive information via email.

## Messaging

If you're a member of this site, you're able to send and receive messages from other members. Messages are relayed through the site, keeping the email addresses of both the sender and the recipient private. However, if either party _chooses_ to share their email address with the other, WarcraftPets.com cannot be held responsible for any misconduct.

**NOTE:** By default, messaging is set to 'enabled', allowing you to send and receive messages. You can disable this setting from your account management page.

## Personal Information

Your personal information will be used solely to process your online activity and to establish any necessary communications via email. Any form of casual communication from our staff that you consider a nuisance will be suspended, per your request.

WarcraftPets.com does everything possible to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, alteration, or destruction.

## Policy Updates

Major changes to this policy will be prominently displayed in the News section.

_**Policy last revised:** 21-Sep-2012_.
